Guide to the Kings County Historic Records Microfilm Collection BCMS.0047
Brooklyn Collection
- Reel 56, Student Papers from the James A. Kelly Institute for Historical Studies at St. Francis College, 1961 (Reel 56)
  - Pantano, Anthony. History of The Brooklyn Academy of Music. (Reel 56)
  - O'Kelly, James S. Brooklyn Theater Fire. (Reel 56)
  - Mason, Thomas J. Law Enforcement in Brooklyn During the English Period. (Reel 56)
  - Martin, Harold J. The Revolution of Jacob Leisler 1689-1691. (Reel 56)
  - Reardon, Alan J. New York Benevolent Despot Governor Richard Nicolls 1664-1668. (Reel 56)
  - McCormick, John J. William Kieft. (Reel 56)
  - Brother Jeremiah. Peter Stuyvesant. (Reel 56)
  - Mastrion, Robert J. History of Epiphany Roman Catholic Church. (Reel 56)
  - Kehoe, Frank. Colonel Alfred W. Wood. (Reel 56)
  - McMahon, James. History of Brooklyn Preparatory High School. (Reel 56)
  - Rose, Cornelius. The Conditions, Accounts and Memorials Concerning the Prison Ship Martyrs of Wallabout Bay 1776-1783. (Reel 56)
  - Castelli, Joseph J. Influence of Hugh McLaughlin on Brooklyn Politics. (Reel 56)
  - Gallagher, Hugh E. The Conquest of Pestilence in Brooklyn 1804-1873. (Reel 56)
  - Jeanne Ellen. The Brooklyn and Long Island Sanitary Fair, 1861. (Reel 56)
  - Anne Kathleen. The Brooklyn Trolley Strick of 1895. (Reel 56)
  - Milewski, John S. Seth Low on Municipal Reform and Civil Service. (Reel 56)
  - Zufolo, Michael-Anthony. Peter Caesar Alberti, The First Italian Settler on Brooklyn. (Reel 56)
- Reel 57, Titles 1-9 are Student Papers from the James A. Kelly Institute for Historical Studies at St. Francis College, 1957 (Reel 57)
  - Keane, Joseph. The First English Period 1664-1673. (Reel 57)
  - Infranco, Anthony. Political Nativism in Brooklyn. (Reel 57)
  - Scotti, Frank Gene. The Third Voyage of Henry Hudson. (Reel 57)
  - Dorsa, Joseph P. Early Land Grants, Deeds and Settlements in the Five Dutch Towns of the Borough of Brooklyn. (Reel 57)
  - Byrne, Thomas F. The Early Catholic Church in Brooklyn. (Reel 57)
  - Butler, Jerome. The Story of Gravesend, It's Settlement and Development. (Reel 57)
  - Goydas, John. The Second Half of English Control 1673-1782. (Reel 57)
  - Guadagno, Vincent. The Indian Period. (Reel 57)
  - Varasano, Robert A. The Discoverer of Brooklyn. (Reel 57)
  - The City that Belongs to the World, 1957 (Reel 57)
  - Lyman, Susan E. The Face of New York., 1955 (Reel 57)
  - Anderw-Ditmas, Charles. Historic Homesteads of Kings County., 1909 (Reel 57)
- Reel 58
  - Town Maps of Brooklyn and Bushwick, 1895-1896 (Reel 58)
  - Flatbush Farm Plans 1-30, circa 1890 (Reel 58)
  - Flatbush New Plans, circa 1890 (Reel 58)
  - New Utrecht New Plans, circa 1890 (Reel 58)
  - Flatlands New Plans, circa 1890 (Reel 58)
  - Kings County, Sketch Plans, circa 1890 (Reel 58)
  - Kings County, Working Plans, circa 1890 (Reel 58)
  - Detailed Estate and Old Farm Lines, Atlas of the City of Brooklyn, Volumes 1-6, 1880 (Reel 58)
- Reel 59, Student Papers from the James A. Kelly Institute for Historical Studies at St. Francis College, 1957 (Reel 59)
  - Todd Shipyard Corporation (Reel 59)
  - Ryan, Patrick M. Courts of Kings County. (Reel 59)
  - Thompson, Robert F. The Domestic History of Brooklyn During the Pre-Revolution Period. (Reel 59)
  - Brother De Manafort. The Development of Transportation in Brooklyn. (Reel 59)
  - Nalewski, Walter. The Rise in Education in Brooklyn from 1860-1898. (Reel 59)
- Reel 60
  - Court and Road Records, 1668-1690 (Reel 60)
- Reel 61, All Records circa 1890 (Reel 61)
  - Brooklyn Farm Plans A-G, 1-76 (Reel 61)
  - Brooklyn File Map A-G, 1-76 (Reel 61)
  - Bushwick Farm Plans 1-33 (Reel 61)
  - Bushwick Map Plans 1-33 (Reel 61)
  - New Lots Farm Plans 1-30 (Reel 61)
  - New Lots Map Plans 1-30 (Reel 61)
  - Gravesend Map Plans 1-48 (Reel 61)
  - Gravesend Farm Plans 1-48 (Reel 61)
  - Gravesend Farm Plan 44 (Reel 61)
  - Flatlands Plans 1-45 (Reel 61)
  - New Utrecht Farm Plans 1-50 (Reel 61)
  - New Utrecht Farm Plan 7 (Reel 61)
  - New Utrecht Map Plans 1-50 (Reel 61)
  - New Utrecht Map Plan 46 (Reel 61)